bundublog.com 2011-06-03

# Privacy Policy | bundublog.com - Free Blog

**Privacy Policy, Bundublog.com**

**January 1, 2010**  
**1\. Introduction**

Unless the context clearly indicates to the contrary, any capitalised term in this Privacy Policy shall bear the same meaning as defined in the Bundublog.com General Terms located at [http://www.bundublog.com](http://www.bundublog.com/) which definitions shall be deemed to have been incorporated herein by reference.

**2\. Compliance with Applicable Law**

Protecting Customer privacy is of utmost importance to Bundublog.com. Accordingly, Bundublog.com has developed this Privacy Policy in order to safeguard the Customer’s personal information and to protect the confidentiality thereof. In so doing, Bundublog.com has taken cognisance of the provisions of the Constitution of the Republic of South Africa Act, 108 of 1996, the Electronic Communications Act, 25 of 2002 and the Protection of Personal Information Bill of 2006 (currently before the South African Law Commission) and the common law so as to ensure compliance with all relevant statutory requirements and best practice under South African law.

**3\. No Liability for Unauthorised Disclosure**

While Bundublog.com will do all things reasonably necessary to protect the Customer’s rights of privacy whilst on the Bundublog.com website, Bundublog.com cannot accept any liability whatsoever for unauthorised or unlawful disclosure of the Customer’s personal and confidential information made by third parties who are not subject to Bundublog.com’s control.

**4\. Personal Information**

For purposes of this Privacy Policy, “personal information means the Customer’s name, surname, address, e-mail address, telephone number, cellphone number, ID number, physical address, company name, contact ID number, credit card or banking details.”

**5\. Consent to Collection**

By accepting the Bundublog.com Hosting Terms, the Customer consents to Bundublog.com’s collection of personal information on an ongoing basis for the continued duration of the Customer’s relationship with Bundublog.com, subject to the limitations set out in this Privacy Policy.

**6\. Types of Personal Information Collected**

Bundublog.com collects personal information when a Customer submits an application form to make use of Bundublog.com’s Services, to become a Reseller of Bundublog.com or to respond to a Bundublog.com survey. If you choose to pay for the Services you order from Bundublog.com by way of debit order, Bundublog.com will request your banking details to include in the periodic debit order transactions. Bundublog.com also collects personal information for purposes of improving its Service offering and for purposes of increasing service efficiency.

**7\. Cookies**

We use cookie technology which comprises tiny pieces of data or a small text file that is stored on your computer’s hard drive and which contains information about you, so that the next time you visit the Bundublog.com website, the cookie reminds us of who you are, enabling us to achieve our goal of providing a valuable online experience to you. You are able to however, disable this cookie technology in your Internet browser.

**8\. Customer Data**

The Customer Data collected by Bundublog.com is used solely in connection with granting you access to the website and for purposes of monitoring the Customer’s use of the website so as to limit or prevent breaches of security.

**9\. Disclosure of Personal Information**

Subject to your right to withdraw your consent in certain instances, you agree that we may obtain your personal information and use it, for certain specified purposes, including for, internal Bundublog.com marketing and contract administration as well as to enable us to collect your debit order payment. We will also provide personal information to law enforcement authorities in response to subpoenas and other lawful requirements where we believe that the disclosure of such personal information is necessary to identify, contact or institute legal proceedings against third parties who jeopardise the provision and rendering of the Services by Bundublog.com.

**10\. Retension of Personal Information**

All personal information will only be retained for as long as it is necessary to fulfil the purposes mentioned in clause 9 above.

**11\. Accurate and Up To Date**

Bundublog.com will use its best endeavours to keep the personal information it collects as accurate, complete and up to date as is necessary for the purposes mentioned in clause 9 above, and Bundublog.com shall, from time to time, request the Customer to update its personal information on the website. You are able to review or update any personally identifiable information that we hold on you by accessing your account via WordPress Dashboard or by e-mailing us or phoning us. Please note that in order to better protect you and safeguard your personal information, we do take steps to verify your identity before granting you access to your account or making any corrections to your personal information.

**12\. Security**

Bundublog.com uses encryption, firewalls and other security technology and procedures to help protect the confidentiality of your personal information and prevent unauthorised access or improper use thereof. All personal information is securely stored in Bundublog.com’s Customer Database.
